Preliminary guide to the Karren Alenier literary papers, 1962 - 2016 MS2223
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Drafts and publications, 1968-2016; Series 2
  - Poetry: New York, Frankfort to Munich, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Poetry: No Chocolate Milk for Kids, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Poetry: Observation, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Poetry: Old Relations, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Poetry: On the Joy of Naming Your Own, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Poetry: One More Day in Peru, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Poetry: Oranges, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Poetry: originals, undated; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Poetry: Outside the Day Was Very Bright(visit with a Berkley carpenter), undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Poetry: Passing Out, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Poetry: Paul Klee, "The Creator", undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Poetry: Phenomenon, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Poetry: Pickled Fantasies or the Realities of Student Life, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Poetry: Piper, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Poetry: Placing the Face with the Myth, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Poetry: Pre Election Thoughts, 1972, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Poetry: Preparing to go to the Beauty Shop, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Poetry: printed works, undated; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Poetry: Procreation, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Poetry: Punting, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Poetry: Putting Dream in the Dressing, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Poetry: Query to Young Russing Gymnist on Uneven Bars, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Poetry: Quest(ion), undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Poetry: Reaching, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Poetry: Renting Chairs in Parc Monsouris, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Poetry: Repetitions, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Poetry: Report to the Owner of a Porsche, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Poetry: Rock Bottom Music, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Poetry: Rolling, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Poetry: Same Old Story(for sol), undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Poetry: Sea Pairs, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Poetry: Seeing the Lisp in the Pecking Order, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Poetry: She Couldn't Explain, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Poetry: Sitting for the Season, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Poetry: Sky Dive, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Poetry: Solving for Y, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Poetry: Solving the Mysteries of the Universe, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Poetry: Spidering, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Poetry: Spring Trip, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Poetry: Stance, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Poetry: Stocking a Different Kind of Ark, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Poetry: Suspension, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Poetry: Taking the Jazz, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Poetry: Tall Tales, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Poetry: The Caterpillar's Song, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Poetry: The Dancing, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Poetry: The Name of ths Dance is: Don't Wake the Baby, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Poetry: The Robber Takes the Lead on 20th Street NW, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Poetry: There Ain't No Father Christmas, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Poetry: There Is, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - Poetry: Thinking (Examining the Roots), undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Poetry: This Season, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Poetry: Thought for a Letter, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Poetry: Treasure Maps, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - Poetry: Trespass, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Poetry: Tryst, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Poetry: Tunnels, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Poetry: Unspoken, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Poetry: View, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Poetry: Visiting, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - Poetry: Waiting, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - Poetry: Waking, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - Poetry: Watching the Cat Fade, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - Poetry: What Should I Give Besides..., undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Poetry: What Year Did You Say This Is?, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - Poetry: When Jesus Loves You At Every Corner, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - Poetry: When the Train Stopped..., undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - Poetry: Where Is She Going?, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Poetry: Working With the Knobs, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Poetry: Writing Table(or a Good Feeling), undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Poetry: Wunkirle (Most Hospitable Woman), undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Poetry: Yahrzeit, a Birth, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Poetry: Yanked: a portrait of Paul Bowles, Circa 2016; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    General
    This item was deposited by the donor in 2017 and the donor stated at this time that for this draft"the front section of Yanked contains 8 poems mostly based on letters written by Paul Bowles. These were NOT included in THE ANIMA OF PAUL BOWLES because when I inquired at his estate, they said only if I quoted exactly would I get permission. So I decided not to try to publish these poems and I wrote 7 others for section 1"
  - Poets in the School, undated; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Publication: Bartleby, 1987; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Publication: Bumper Cars, 1996; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Publication: Connections, 2001; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Publication: Darkmoon Lilith, 2003; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Publication: Folio, 1986; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Publication: Frantic Egg, 2000 August; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Publication: Gerturude Stein Invents a Jump Early On, undated; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Publication: the Cream of the Troubadour Coffee House, 1990; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Publication: the Crescent Review, 1989; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Publication: the Crescent Review, 1989; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Publication: the Dancers Muse, 1981; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Publication: the Ear's Chamber, 1981; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Publication:Blackwater Review, 1996; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Publications, undated; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Publications, undated; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Publications: Calvert, undated; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Publications: G.W. Review, 1981-1984; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Publications: Happy, 1995; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Publications: Hudson Valley Echos, 1990; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Publications: Israel Horizons, undated; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Publications: Jewish Currents, 1992-1994; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Publications: Jewish Woman's Literary Annual, 1997; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Publications: Lightning Ash, 1996; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Publications: Macguffin, 1994; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Publications: Metiphors, 1998; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Publications: Minimus, 1996-1998; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Publications: Mississippi Review, 1990; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Publications: Mississippi Rivew, 1990; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Publications: Pembroke Magazine, 1997; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Publications: Poet Lore, 1990-1991; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Publications: Quantum Tao, 1998; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Publications: River Run, 1972; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Publications: Spectrum, 1981; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Publications: Sulfur River, 1981; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Publications: Superstition Myth anf Magik, 1996; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Publications: the Pittsburgh Quarterly, 1991; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Publications: The Thursday Book, undated; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Publications: Union Street Review, 1991; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Publications: Whiskey Island, 1990; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Publications: Word Wrights, 1987; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Publications: Word Writes, undated; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Publicatoins: Mediphors, 1998; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Publicatoins: Monocacy Valley Review, 1988; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Salome: A Literary Dance magazine, 1976; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Salome: A Literary Dance magazine, 1978; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Salome: A Literary Dance magazine, 1980; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Salome: A Literary Dance magazine, 1984; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Shall I have the Pleasure: submissions, correspondence, undated; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Sheet music, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Short stories, undated; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Short stories/newspaper clippings, undated; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Short story: Afterbirth, undated; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Short story edited: Spirits, 1997; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Short story: Death of a Big Dog, undated; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Short story: Inventions, undated; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Short story: Reflections, 1996; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Short story: Salary Girl, undated; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Short story: the Mitzvah, undated; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Song: Why Voyeurs are Incurable, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Soul-Loss, undated; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Submission: cookbook proposal, undated; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Submissions, clippings, undated; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - The Monocacy Valley Review, 1987-1988; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - The Steiny Road to Operadom binder with comments, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - The Steiny Road to Operadom with comments, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - The Steiny Road to Operadom with comments, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - The Steiny Road to Operadom with comments, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - The Steiny Road to Operadom, Appendix A, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - The Steiny Road to Operadom, Appendix B, C, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - The Steiny Road to Operadom, chapters 11-20, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - The Steiny Road to Operadom, chapters 1-4, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - The Steiny Road to Operadom, chapters 21-30, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - The Steiny Road to Operadom, chapters 5-10, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Steiny Road to Operadom: The Making of American Operas, 2006; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Traveling pamphlets, brochures, undated; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - VHS tape: Steing Poetry Libreto, undated; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Word works materials, undated; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Word works materials, undated; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Works in progress, clippings, undated; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Works submitted for publishing, undated; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Correspondence, Series 3
  Arranged loosely chronologial. Most folders do not have dates supplied.
  - Postcards, 1979-2001; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, 1984; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, 1986; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, 1987; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, 1988; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, 1988; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Correspindence, misc. materials, 1988; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, 1989; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, 1989; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, 1989; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, 1989; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, 1990; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, 1990; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, 1990; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, 1992; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, 1992; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, 1993; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, 1993; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, 1994; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, 1994; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, 1994; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, 1995; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, 1995; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence [trip to Santa Fe, and other topics], 2010; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: postcards, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: publishing "Cry", undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Clippings, correspondence, undated; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence: postcards, cards, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence: postcards, cards, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: postcards, cards, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence: postcards, cards, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence: postcards, cards, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence: postcards, cards, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence: postcards, cards, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence: submission rejections, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence: poetry submissions, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence: public readings, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence: invitations, undated; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Pamphlets, fliers and correspondence, undated; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, programs, fliers, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Corespondence, undated; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, undated; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, fliers, public perfomances, undated; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: cards, undated; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: cards, undated; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, misc. materials, undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Workshops and conferences, 1980-2007; Series 4
  - American Writers Congress agenda, 1981; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Baltimore Writers Alliance membership directory, 1999-2000; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Conference on Science and Literature, 1981 November 10; Series 4 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - COSMEP materials, undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - COSMEP, California conference, undated; Series 4 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Getting into Print: yong writers conference, undated; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Grant applications, undated; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - International Society of Poets, 2007; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Lifting Belly High Women's Poetry Since 1900 Duquesne University, 2008 September 11-13; Series 4 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Performance workshop, undated; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Poetry Society of America membership list, 1981-1983; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Prague Summer Writers Workshop, 1995; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Snapshots: COSMEP, undated; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Summer in Morocco materials, 1982; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - The Influences of Science and Technology on Literature Seminar materials, 1980 May 09; Series 4 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Workshop materials, undated; Series 4 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Workshop materials, undated; Series 4 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Writers Block workshops, undated; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Young writers conference, undated; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Personal records, Series 5
  - Address books, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Collected stamps, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Contracts for winners, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Day timers, undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Day timers, undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Day timers, undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Day timers, undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Day timers, undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Day timers, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Day timers, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Day timers, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Day timers, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Day timers, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Day timers, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Day timers, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Day timers, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Day timers, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Day timers, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Day timers, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Day timers, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Day timers, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Day-timers, 2002; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Day-timers, 2003; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Day-timers, 2004; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Day-timers, 2005; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Day-timers, 2006; Series 5 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Day-timers, 2007; Series 5 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Day-timers, 2008; Series 5 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Day-timers, 2009; Series 5 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Day-timers, 2010; Series 5 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Day-timers, 2011; Series 5 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Grant proposal submissions, undated; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Journal of forms management, 1985; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Memo book, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Notebook, undated; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Notebook, undated; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Notebook, undated; Series 5 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Notebook: guests at Montgomery Gallery, 1995 October 28; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Notebook: list of books read, undated; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Notebook: Magical Places in Mythical Italy, 1994 June 22 - 1994 July 10; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Notebook: Modern Poetry, undated; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Notebook: philosophy class work, 1968; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Periodical: Potpouri, 1992; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Script for wedding, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Travel, undated; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Travel diaries and notes, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Travel diaries and notes, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Travel diaries and notes, undated; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Wedding reception materials, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Publicity and marketing, Series 6
  - Art shows/exhibits materials, undated; Series 6 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, undated; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Dance view materials, undated; Series 6 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Fliers, poetry readings, undated; Series 6 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Looking for Devine Transportation poster, undated; Series 6 (Box 18)
  - Marketing, undated; Series 6 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Martin E. Segal Theatre Center, City University of New York, 2008; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Miller Cabin, 1985; Series 6 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Moving Words awards ceremony and poetry reading, 2006; Series 6 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Pamphlets and other ephemra, undated; Series 6 (Box 7, Folder 15)